

### ······Contact

mihretab.habtemichael@motopp.nl Web - https://github.com/Z-Michael

#### HYWW 'Skills'

Mendix'
HTML'
CSS'
xUj UgWfJdh'
6cchghfUd'
K cfXdfYgg
G'UW'
CZZWY' \* \$
Git

### GcZh'G\_]``g

GY ZA chij UhYX HYUa d'UnYf 8YV||g]cb AU\_er Waaib]cator

## Languages<sup>\*</sup>

Nederlands (6%) English(9I W``Ybh)



### Mihreteab Habtemichael

Netherlands, Hilversum

#### **Profile**

='Ua'U'AYbX]I'8Yj Y`cdYf"='Ua'ZUgV]JbUhYX`VmhYW\bc`c[]Yg`UbX''dfc[fUa a]b[``Ub[i U[Yg"=\Uj Y`Ghi X]YX`Dmh\cb`Dfc[fUa a]b[`k]h\ h\fYY'\Wfh]ZJ\WhYg"Bchcb`mh\Uhž\Vi h='U'gc'a UXY`U'ZYk kYVg]hYg`Zcf'a mgY`Z'UbX'YIYfV]JgYX`h\Y'dfc[fUa a]b[``Ub[i U[Yg'h\Uh=\Uj Y'ghi X]YX``]\_Y'>Uj UGWf]dhž'<HA@UbX`7GG"'G]bWf'>Ubi Ufmž=[ch'U'k cbXYfZi`cddcfhi b]hmhc`VY'U'AYbX]I'XYj Y`cdYf"'AYbX]I']g'h\Y'Zi hifY'd`UhZcfa 'Zcf'kYVg]hY'hY\W\bc`c[]Yg'k]h\'U'ai`h]Zi b\W]cbU``UbX`ZYI]V`Y''d`UhZcfa "='Ua'gc'dUgg]cbUhY'hc`YUfb`UbX'hc'g\ck'a mg\_]`g']b'hYUa g'UbX`UXX'j U'i Y"'

### Motopp Mendix Advanced Developer Accelerator Program

202

We have been taught to use the Mendix platform. We have built a Mendix app from scratch, where we had to collaborate with a Product Owner to finalize the requirements and convert those into a working and business/user centric application. While executing the project we have joined several Mendix courses and lectures for further knowledge extension. Whi ch was directly put into practice in their Mendix project.

- Certification
- Agile working
- ALMÁ
- Team Server
- VersioningÁ
- BranchingÁ
- DomainÁ modellingÁ
- DataÁ normalizationÁ

- Security verification
- Account handling
- Front-endÁ developmentÁ
- Page buildingÁ
- Data bindingÁ
- StylingÁ
- Microflow modellingÁ

- Data processing
- Data generation
- QueryingÁ
- Integration Rest,Á Excel, filingÁ
- Modelling bestÁ practicingÁ
- Process modelling
- Action orientatedÁ modellingÁ

#### **Education**

\* &\$\$, !20%((Ethiopia))!6UW(Y`cf`cZ7ca di hYf`5dd`]\Wh]cbg` fEquivalent to Netherlands <6C LevelŁ

#### **Certificates**

- \* Python Fundamental
- \* Python Data Structure
- \* Python Data Base

## **Work Experience**

- \* 2011-2012 (*Ethiopia*) -Worked as a Library Network Administrator.
- \* 2020-2021 as a WordPress Developer
- \* Monitoring website performance and handling troubleshooting and News feed update . https://educationrunway.nl/nl/
- \* 2020-2021- Junior AI-Operator at MediaPark.

## **Voluntarily Jobs**

- \* Education Runaway(https://educationrunway.nl/nl/) board member.
- \* Computer and Smart phones installation/Maintenance.
- \* Translation language from Tigregna to Dutch/English.
- \* Basic computer Training for Eritrean Residences in Hilversum

# My Background

I came to The Netherlands around 2013. I had a long Asylum procedure and It was a rough time to accomplish my dreams. At Asylum seekers center i have been helping on translating and teaching other refugees a basic computers skills. Since 2018 i got my residence permit and my life got back on track. I started learning Dutch and focused on self studying (web develop ment) and related ICT technologies While i am doing self development; I started to look for a new, promising field in which I would take great pleasure to improve myself and where i could build something. And as the great chance of my life, I met Motopp. Mendix is exactly what I was looking for and started my journey on 2022 as Mendix Developer.